# **MIQUEL SUAU GONZÀLEZ**

Barcelona, Spain · +34 611 48 22 45 · sq.miquel@gmail.com · linkedin.com/in/miquel-suau-gonzalez

GitHub: https://github.com/MayKoder Portfolio: https://maykoder.github.io/maykoder/

Software developer and game programmer. Professional experience with Flutter and as a full-stack engineer. Unbreakable passion for programming. I take my role extremely seriously, and I have no difficulties communicating with all the different fields of the sector.

Furthermore, I have a shining work ethic that puts quality and performance at the top of the priority list. I'm an excellent team player, but I also have enough organization skills and working ethic to resolve issues and deliver deadlines on my own if necessary.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

The Brain Therapy, Barcelona, Spain

2021 - Present

#### **Intern to Junior Software Developer**

• Started as an intern for the startup and developed with my boss' supervision the main app and all the frontend (all screens and interactions with the app) and backend code. Developed a Python firebase manager for non-programmers management. Currently, a Junior dev.

Valking, Barcelona, Spain

2021-2022

## **Mobile Application Developer**

 Developed 3 apps with flutter with another teammate. Dealt with front and back end and programmed the database code. The apps were an automatic upgrade and two production ready apps for subscriptions and video streaming.

Lateral Thinking Code, Terrassa, Spain

2019-2019

#### **Programming Tutor**

• Worked during the summer break as a coding teacher with various languages and platforms with 10-16 year old kids. Achieved a teacher grade of average 96% of student satisfaction.

#### **TOP ACHIEVEMENTS**

**Diamond Engine** 

Jun 2021

• Engine developed in 4 months from scratch. Has MonoRuntime and C# linking and shader scripting. Supports every basic engine feature.

### The Mandalorian: Ashes of the Empire

Jan 2021

 All class projects were made in 4 months. My role was to be the code leader and manage the 20-person team. My engine was used for the project and was upgraded by the code department and me, adding post-processing, shadow mapping and more features.

#### **EDUCATION**

Centre de la Imatge i la Tecnologia Multimèdia, Terrassa, Spain

2018-2022

## **Bachelor's degrees in Video Game Design and Development**

- Awards: Honors grade PROGIVJ (only 2 awarded to class), Best game engine (Only 1 awarded in class)
- Completed one-semester study abroad with Glasgow Caledonian University

#### **SKILLS & OTHER**

**Skills:** C, C++, C#, Java, JavaScript, Python, Flutter, GLSL, Unity, Unreal Engine, GitHub, Maya, Firebase, Jira, OpenGL, Tkinter, SDL, HTML, CSS, MonoRuntime

**Languages:** Native in Spanish; Native in Catalan; C1 certified in English **Volunteering:** Volunteered as event assistant at Canòdrom for a week (2021).